{
    "isLoggedIn": false,
    "surveys": {
        "test": {
            "title": "Test Survey",
            "description": "The default test survey",
            "questions": {
                "Q-1": {
                    "question": "What is your name?",
                    "type": "text",
                    "answers": ["test", "Jayton"]
                },
                "Q-2": {
                    "question": "How many stars is Subway?",
                    "type": "number",
                    "max": "3",
                    "min": "0",
                    "answers": [0, 1]
                },
                "Q-3": {
                    "question": "Favourite ice cream flavour?",
                    "type": "choice",
                    "choices": {
                        "Q-3-Ch-1": {
                            "choice": "Vanilla"
                        },
                        "Q-3-Ch-2": {
                            "choice": "Chocolate"
                        },
                        "Q-3-Ch-3": {
                            "choice": "Mint"
                        }
                    },
                    "answers": ["Vanilla", "Mint"]
                }
            }
        },
        "pets": {
            "title": "Pets",
            "description": "A simple survey about your pets",
            "questions": {
                "Q-1": {
                    "question": "Do you own any pets?",
                    "type": "choice",
                    "choices": {
                        "Q-1-Ch-1": { "choice": "Yes" },
                        "Q-1-Ch-2": { "choice": "No" }
                    },
                    "answers": ["Yes"]
                },
                "Q-2": {
                    "question": "How many?",
                    "type": "number",
                    "max": "10",
                    "min": "0",
                    "choices": { "Q-2-Ch-1": {}, "Q-2-Ch-2": {} },
                    "answers": [1]
                },
                "Q-3": {
                    "question": "What is your favourite animal?",
                    "type": "choice",
                    "choices": {
                        "Q-3-Ch-1": { "choice": "Cat" },
                        "Q-3-Ch-2": { "choice": "Dog" },
                        "Q-3-Ch-3": { "choice": "Turtle" },
                        "Q-3-Ch-4": { "choice": "Panda" },
                        "Q-3-Ch-5": { "choice": "Bunny" },
                        "Q-3-Ch-6": { "choice": "Fish" }
                    },
                    "answers": ["Cat"]
                },
                "Q-4": {
                    "question": "Tell me a story about a Pet",
                    "type": "text",
                    "answers": ["She is crazy!"]
                }
            }
        },
        "movie": {
            "title": "Movies",
            "description": "A simple movie survey!",
            "questions": {
                "Q-4": {
                    "question": "What is your favourite movie?",
                    "type": "text",
                    "answers": ["Pirates"]
                },
                "Q-6": {
                    "question": "What is your least favourite movie?",
                    "type": "text",
                    "answers": ["N/A"]
                },
                "Q-7": {
                    "question": "How do you score \"A New Hope\"?",
                    "type": "number",
                    "max": "10",
                    "min": "1",
                    "answers": [6]
                }
            }
        }
    }
}
